Guide to the Ephemera collection, 1835-2002 MS2380
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Ephemera, 1835-2002; Series 2
  - The charities of Washington by Mrs. Senator W.H. Blair., Circa [1887]; Series 2; pages 25-27; 30 cm (Box 7, Folder 49)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 347
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Detached from: Chautauquan (Jamestown, N.Y.). Oct. 1887.
    Subjects: Charities Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2009118776; Charities. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00852404; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - Nat and his break-neck hurry: a postmaster's race over Washington cobblestones in pre-asphaltic times., Circa [1894]; Series 2; pages [49]-54: illustrations; 23 cm (Box 7, Folder 50)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 348
    Cataloger notes: Caption title.; Detached from: Good roads. Vol. 5. numbers 2 (Feb. 1894).
  - A guide to the painting and sculpture in the Justice Department Building, Washington, District of Columbia., Circa [1938]; Series 2; 27 pages: illustrations, plates, maps; 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 51)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 349
    Subjects: United States. Department of Justice Guidebooks. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79038419; United States. Department of Justice. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01852803; Robert F. Kennedy Building Guidebooks. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/no2014131986; Art Washington (D.C.); Art, American Washington (D.C.); Mural painting and decoration, American Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85088545; Public buildings Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145360; Art, American. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00815895; Art. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00815177; Guidebooks. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01423871
  - A Guide to the painting and sculpture in the Post Office Department Building, Washington, District of Columbia., Circa [1938]; Series 2; 32, xii pages: illustrations, 1 plan, 1 map; 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 52)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 350
    Cataloger notes: Cover title: Art guides: Post Office Department.
    Subjects: United States. Post Office Department Art collections.; Art Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2007101385; Painting, American. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85096685; Public art Washington (D.C.); Sculpture, American. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85119028
  - Special libraries. Vol. 19, numbers 5 (May-June, 1928), Washington number., Circa [1928]; Series 2; pages [137]-165: illustrations, map; 28 cm (Box 7, Folder 53)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 351
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; District of Columbia Collection of the Washington Public Library / by Emma Hance -- Federal city to national capital / by Louise P. Latimer -- Knowledge tours of Washington / by Elizabeth O. Cullen -- Library of Congress notes / by Frederick W. Ashley -- Public documents library / by Mary B. Hartwell -- Washington of tomorrow / by Major Carey H. Brown -- Conference -- Notes -- Departments.
    Subjects: Special Libraries Association. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79076742; Special Libraries Association. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00534693; Libraries Washington (D.C.); Libraries. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00997341; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - Chase's. Vol. 6, numbers 22 (Week of Feb. 8, 1904)., Circa [1904]; Series 2; 32 unnumbered pages: illustrations; 27 cm (Box 7, Folder 54)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 352
    Cataloger notes: "P.B. Chase, proprietor ... devoted to Mr. Chase's original idea, polite vaudeville ..."; Cover title.; Includes vaudeville program and many advertisements.
    Subjects: Vaudeville Washington (D.C.); Vaudeville. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01164609; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - The government's failure as a builder by Montgomery Schuyler., Circa [1894]; Series 2; pages [609]-621; 24 cm (Box 7, Folder 55)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 353
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Detached from: The forum. July, 1894.
    Subjects: Public buildings United States. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85140485; Public buildings. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01082090; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - Birds of the Washington, D.C., region by May Thacher Cooke., 1929; Series 2; 79 pages: tables; 24 cm. (Box 7, Folder 56)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 354
    Cataloger notes: Includes bibliographical references (pages 68-73).
  - Washington -- the Capitol., Undated; Series 2; pages 289-290; 25 cm. (Box 7, Folder 57)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 355
    Cataloger notes: In Ladies' garland (Philadelphia, Pa.). Vol. 1, numbers 16 (May 1838).
    Subjects: Van Buren, Martin, 1782-1862 Inauguration, 1837.; Van Buren, Martin, 1782-1862. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00054740; United States Capitol (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85141041; United States Capitol (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00631067; 1837 fast; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743
  - A federal employee's guide to housing in Washington., 1967; Series 2; 20 pages: illustrations, maps; 27 cm (Box 7, Folder 58)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 356
    Cataloger notes: "HUD MP-10"--Page 4 of cover.; "January 1967"--Page 4 of cover.; Cover title.
    Subjects: Housing Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008121997; Housing. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00962245; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - The Indians of Arlington., 1957; Series 2; 30 pages illustrations 22 cm (Box 7, Folder 59)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 357
    Cataloger notes: Includes bibliographical references.
    Subjects: Indians of North America Virginia. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh89002072; Antiquities. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00810745; Indians of North America. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00969633; Arlington County (Va.) Antiquities.; Virginia Arlington County. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01219848; Virginia. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204597
  - Historic Georgetown annual house tour, 1950., Circa [1950]; Series 2; 32 pages: illustrations; 22 cm (Box 7, Folder 60)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 358
    Subjects: Dwellings Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85040265; Dwellings. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00899978; Georgetown (Washington, D.C.) Tours.; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Washington (D.C.) Georgetown. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01314225; Tours. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423866
  - Our church: established 1803 New York Avenue Presbyterian church, Washington, D.C., Circa [1948?]; Series 2; 28 pages: illustrations, portrait; 28 cm (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 359
    Subjects: New York Avenue Presbyterian Church (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n87111278; New York Avenue Presbyterian Church (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00626209; Church buildings Washington (D.C.); Church buildings. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00860599; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - Section room management., 1939; Series 2; 7 pages; 20 cm (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 360
    Subjects: Central High School (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n2003075017; Central High School (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00779374; School management and organization Washington (D.C.); School management and organization. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01107575; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - 312th Machine Gun Battalion: "Washington's own": what they did and how they did it by compiled from data furnished through the courtesy of former Sergt. Major William Hennessay., Circa [1921?]; Series 2; 20 pages; 18 cm (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 361
    Cataloger notes: "Souvenir number."; Cover title.
    Subjects: United States. Army. Machine Gun Battalion, 312th.; World War, 1914-1918 Regimental histories United States. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008113788
  - Trends in curriculum development: address at the Cooperative Spring Conference of the Educational Associations of the District of Columbia by George H. Reavis., Circa [1941]; Series 2; 16 pages; 21 cm (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 362
    Subjects: Curriculum planning. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85034895; Curriculum planning. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00885382
  - Curriculum revision on the senior high school level: an address delivered before the Teachers' Institute by Thomas W. Gosling., Circa [1938]; Series 2; 12 pages; 20 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 364
  - A provisional guidance program for the senior high schools, Washington, D.C. approved by the Board of Education., Circa [1939]; Series 2; 7 pages; 21 cm (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 365
    Subjects: Educational counseling Washington (D.C.); High schools Washington (D.C.); Educational counseling. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00903395; High schools. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00956288; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - Courses of study in the high and manual training schools, Washington, D.C. by Board of Education, District of Columbia., Circa [1907?]; Series 2; 20 unnumbered pages; 23 cm (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 366
    Subjects: High schools Washington (D.C.); Vocational education Washington (D.C.); High schools. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00956288; Vocational education. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01168486; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - Information relative to the survey and evaluation of the Eastern High School: November 24, 25, 26, 1941 [edited and prepared for publication by Kate C. Moore and Mary C. Mason]., Circa [1941]; Series 2; 74 pages: illustrations; 18 cm (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 367
    Subjects: Eastern High School (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n2012023641; High schools Washington (D.C.)
  - Fiftieth anniversary, Zion Evangelical Lutheran Church: June third to eighth, 1917, Washington, D.C., Circa [1917]; Series 2; 12 unnumbered pages: illustrations, portraits; 24 cm (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 368
    Subjects: Zion Evangelical Lutheran Church (Washington, D.C.); Church buildings Washington (D.C.)
  - Arlington by William Edgar Rogers., Circa [1908]; Series 2; pages [2]-12: illustrations; 26 cm (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 370
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Detached from: Republic magazine. Vol. 1, numbers 5 (May 1908).
    Subjects: Arlington National Cemetery (Arlington, Va.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n88155885; Arlington National Cemetery (Arlington, Va.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00652507; Cemeteries Virginia Arlington.; Cemeteries. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00850521; Virginia Arlington. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01205304
  - An old Virginia town., 1881; Series 2; pages 489-502; 25 cm. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 371
    Cataloger notes: Description of Alexandria during the colonial period.
    Subjects: Manners and customs. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01007815; Travel. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01155558; Alexandria (Va.) Description and travel.; Alexandria (Va.) Social life and customs.; Virginia Alexandria. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01206236
  - Graduation exercises: Thursday, January the twenty-ninth, nineteen hundred twenty-five at eight o'clock: Central High School, Washington, D.C., Circa [1925]; Series 2; 4 unnumbered pages; 24 cm (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 372
    Subjects: Central High School (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n2003075017; Central High School (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00779374; Schools Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008110244; Schools. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01107958; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - Report of the Board of Metropolitan Police for the year 1865., Circa [1865]; Series 2; pages [842]-854; 23 cm (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 373
    Cataloger notes: Caption title.; Detached from: Report of the Secretary of the Interior for the year 1865. [Washington: Govt. Print. Off., 1865].
    Subjects: Washington (D.C.). Police Department.; Police Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2010106860
  - Gallery Place: urban design alternatives for development at a forthcoming subway stop in downtown Washington, D.C. by [Urban Design Studio, Dept. of Architecture and Planning, Catholic University of America]., Circa [1972]; Series 2; 8 unnumbered pages: illustrations; 22 x 28 cm (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 376
  - Handbook of the libraries in the District of Columbia compiled by H.H.B. Meyer, Chief Bibliographer, in cooperation with the D.C. Library Association., 1914; Series 2; 64 pages; 17 cm (Box 8, Folder 15)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 377
    Cataloger notes: At head of title: Library of Congress.; Includes index.; The handbook of the District of Columbia Library Association, 1897 and its supplement 1898 included notes on libraries in Washington.
    Subjects: Libraries Washington (D.C.); Libraries. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00997341; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01204505
  - Washington's Italian community, 1890-present: an exhibit prepared by the Center for Washington Area Studies at the George Washington University., Circa [1984]; Series 2; 1 folded sheet (4 pages): illustrations, portraits; 22 x 28 cm (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 378
    Cataloger notes: Exhibited at: Holy Rosary Church, Nov. 10-11, 1984 and Washingtoniana Division, Martin Luther King Library, Nov. 13-Dec. 31, 1984.
    Subjects: Italian Americans Washington (D.C.) Exhibitions.; Italian Americans. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00980419; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Exhibition catalogs. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01424028
  - The case of Guiteau, assassin of the President of the United States by Charles F. Folsom., Undated; Series 2; pages 145-153, [1] leaf of plates: portraits; 28 cm. (Box 8, Folder 17)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 379
    Cataloger notes: In Boston medical and surgical journal. Boston: Cupples, Upham. Vol. 106, numbers 7 (Feb. 16, 1882).
    Subjects: Garfield, James A. (James Abram), 1831-1881 Assassination.; Guiteau, Charles J. (Charles Julius), 1841-1882. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n50018818; Garfield, James A. (James Abram), 1831-1881. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00004703; Guiteau, Charles J. (Charles Julius), 1841-1882. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01898134; Assassination. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00818962
  - The workingman's advocate, extra: a monthly publication devoted to the political and social advancement of the masses. Sept. 15, 1840., Circa [1840]; Series 2; pages [65]-80: illustrations; 22 cm (Box 8, Folder 18)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 380
    Cataloger notes: Caption title.; British Whig trap to catch voters!
    Subjects: 1837 - 1841 fast; Politics and government fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01919741; United States Politics and government 1837-1841. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85140431; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - Washington's facilities for training in library science: a report by the Committee on library training., Circa 1923; Series 2; 11 pages; 20 cm (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 381
    Cataloger notes: Clara W. Herbert, chairman.
    Subjects: Library schools Washington (D.C.); Library schools. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00997907; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - Washington life. Vol. 1, numbers 1 (Dec. 1, 1935)., Circa [1935]; Series 2; 34 pages: illustrations, portraits; 29 cm (Box 8, Folder 20)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 382
    Cataloger notes: Caption title.; What's going on! -- Politically speaking / by C.N. Heare -- 30 seconds to go / by K. Hillyer -- Society / by Madame Sonja -- Intimate interviews / by Marhsall Fink -- Theatres / by Ed Amard -- Night clubs / by C.A. Baret.
  - National Cycle Track Association, 1898., Series 2; 136 unnumbered pages: illustrations, portraits; 23 cm (Box 8, Folder 21)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 383
    Cataloger notes: Washington Athletic Park, Washington, D.C.
    Subjects: National Cycle Track Association.; Cycling United States.; Cycling Washington (D.C.)
  - The Women's voice: a national women's magazine published in the interests of Republican polices. Vol. 1, numbers 1 (May 1939)., Series 2; 24 pages: illustrations, portraits; 24 cm (Box 8, Folder 22)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 384
    Subjects: 1933 - 1945 fast; Women Political activity United States. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008113699; Politics and government fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01919741; Women Political activity. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01734136; United States Politics and government 1933-1945. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85140464; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - Handkerchief map of Washington to aid George Washington Memorial Parkway., Circa [1933?]; Series 2; 2 unnumbered pages: illustrations, map; 25 cm (Box 8, Folder 23)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 385
    Subjects: George Washington Memorial Parkway (Va. and Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85054206; Washington (D.C.) Maps. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008117384; United States George Washington Memorial Parkway. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01333569; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Maps. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423704
  - The Washington amateur magazine: a magazine devoted to the interests of the boys and girls of the country. Vol. 1, numbers 6 (Dec. 1872)., Circa [1872]; Series 2; pages [81]-95; 24 cm (Box 8, Folder 24)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 386
    Subjects: Children's literature. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2011002478; Children's literature. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01759351
  - Prince George's County Maryland: for flights of fancy and down to earth adventure., Circa [1985]; Series 2; 1 folded sheet (6 pages): color illustrations, color map; 23 cm (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 387
    Subjects: Travel. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01155558; Prince George's County (Md.) Description and travel.; Maryland Prince George's County. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01207053
  - The American government by Albert Bushnell Hart., Circa [1917]; Series 2; pages [1]-11, [6] leaves of plates: illustrations; 26 cm. (Box 8, Folder 26)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 388
    Cataloger notes: In Mentor (Mentor Association (New York, N.Y.)). Vol. 5, numbers 20 (Dec. 1, 1917).
    Subjects: Politics and government fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01919741; Travel. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01155558; United States Politics and government. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85140410; Washington (D.C.) Description and travel. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145349; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - Capital almanac 1893., Circa [1893]; Series 2; 40 pages: illustrations; 21 cm (Box 8, Folder 27)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 389
    Subjects: Almanacs, American Washington (D.C.); Almanacs, American. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00805775; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - The Medical Center news. Vol. 1, numbers 2 (Feb. 15, 1939)., Circa [1939]; Series 2; 12 pages: illustrations; 28 cm (Box 8, Folder 28)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 390
    Subjects: Hospitals Washington (D.C.); Medical centers Washington (D.C.); Hospitals. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00961166; Medical centers. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01013928; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - The Republic: a monthly magazine, devoted to the dissemination of political information. Vol. 6, numbers 6 (June, 1876)., Circa [1876]; Series 2; pages [337]-400, iv pages; 23 cm (Box 8, Folder 29)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 391
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Includes index.; Bryan, W.B. Bibliography of the District of Columbia, pages 158
    Subjects: 1865 - 1877 fast; Politics and government fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01919741; United States Politics and government 1865-1877. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85140443; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - Title 34 prepared by the Sexuality Task Force of the Washington, D.C. Chapter of the National Organization for Women., 1975; Series 2; 2 folded sheets (10 pages); 28 cm (Box 8, Folder 30)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 392
    Cataloger notes: English and Spanish.
    Subjects: Washington (D.C.). Title 34. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79018774; Discrimination Law and legislation Washington (D.C.)
  - D.C. Bicentennial Commission meeting, February 26, 1973., Circa [1973]; Series 2; 42 unnumbered pages; 30 cm (Box 8, Folder 31)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 394
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Agenda for the February 26 meeting of the Bicentennial Commission of the District of Columbia -- Minutes, Dec. 18, 1972 -- Financial report -- Overall program thrust -- First year program and resource relationships.
    Subjects: American Revolution Bicentennial (1976) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01709740; 1976 fast; American Revolution Bicentennial, 1976 Washington (D.C.); Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - Historic points of interest selected by the Committee on Marking Points of Historic Interest for the Presidential Inauguration., Circa [190-?]; Series 2; 16 pages; 16 cm (Box 8, Folder 32)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 395
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Portions of front and back covers missing; thus date of publication missing.
    Subjects: Historic buildings Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85061106; Historic sites Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85061141; Historic buildings. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00957723; Historic sites. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00957846; Washington (D.C.) Guidebooks. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008117391; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Guidebooks. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423871
  - Floral concert: Miss Julia A. Childs, with a class of forty young lads and misses, will give a floral concert ..., Circa [18--]; Series 2; 1 broadside; 30 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 33)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 397
    Subjects: Concerts. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85030620; Concerts. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00874069; Broadsides. rbgenr; Programs. rbgenr
  - Howard Athenaeum, Howard Street., Circa [185-?]; Series 2; 1 broadside; 31 x 15 cm (Box 8, Folder 34)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 399
    Cataloger notes: Undated program for 3 theatrical presentations.